https://www.axiell.com/privacy-policy/

Read the report: Culture at a Crossroads, Digital Transformation in the Age of COVID-19
Read the report: Culture at a Crossroads, Digital Transformation in the Age of COVID-19
Change added on 28 May 2018
We may share the personal information we collect through our Sites for marketing and information purposes as described below:
Our Service Providers. We share personal information with companies and organizations, including subsidiaries and other business entities controlled by Axiell, that perform services on our behalf, for example, companies that provide website support services to us. For some of these services (like the public social networks), we leverage their services for our social accounts connected to Axiell. The management of personal data is related to how the service themselves manage the data.
Change added on 4 May 2018
We’re now taking this opportunity to update the our Terms of Service and European Privacy Policy which outline the rules for using Axiell Websites and our relationship with you. If you are located in the European Union (EU) or the European Economic Area (EEA), the European Privacy Policy applies to you.
The updates are part of our work to comply with the new General Data Protection Regulation. These updates help you better understand how we collect and manage your data. As of 25 May 2018, you will be given the opportunity to more easily control your data and how it is being used.
The updated Terms of Service and Privacy Policy go into effect on 25 May 2018. If you continue to use any of Axiell Websites on or after 25 May 2018, you are agreeing to the updated Terms of Service and our use of your data as set out in our Privacy Policy. If you don’t want the updated Terms of Service and Privacy Policy to apply to you, you can click the button to decline using cookies and will be directed to a light version of our website with limited functionality and limited information.
We are making it easier for you to control the cookies being used and stored and will have the option to only submit certain cookies by changing our cookie consent forms and you now have direct access to which cookies are being used.
We have added IP-Adress as a type of “Personal Information”.
Changes added on 7 December 2017
Right to erasure (‘right to be forgotten’): You have right to request from us erasure of personal data or restriction of processing and to object to processing as well as the right to data portability. For information about how to get access to Personal Data and for exercising your rights, please refer to the contact points mentioned at the end of this Privacy Notice.
Changes added on 6 December 2016
Axiell uses cookies to analyse traffic to this website. Therefore we are sharing information about how you use our website with third party suppliers, like Google and others.
We use cookies to adapt the content of our site, and advertisement to the visitors of the site, apply functions for social media and analyse our traffic. We collect and send information about your usage of our site to those Social media, advertising and analysis companies we cooperate with. These companies can in their turn combine this information with other information you have shared or they have collected when their services have been in use.
Axiell’s Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. This Online Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains how we protect your privacy when you visit this Web site and the other Axiell Web sites that display this Privacy Policy (our “Site(s)”). This Privacy Policy describes what types of information we gather and track when you use our Sites, how this information is used and with whom it is shared. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
This site is operated by the Axiell company established in the country to which the content of the site is directed. If the site is not directed to a specific country, the Swedish law and European Privacy Act will be applied. A list of the countries to which the content of the site is directed can be found on the following page: www.axiell.com/contact. (You may also access this page by clicking on the “contact” link at the top of each page). If you are accessing a page of the site directed at a particular EU country, the legal name and contact details of the EU Axiell company operating the site in respect of that EU country can be found on the relevant country page. (For some EU countries, this may be an Axiell company established in a different country). The Axiell company operating the site in respect of a particular EU country is also the data controller in respect of personal data collected through that part of the site. This Axiell company is referred to in this Privacy Policy as “Axiell,” “we,” “us,” and “our”.
Scope of This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy covers the “personal information” we collect through our Sites.
“Personal information” is information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to us. Examples of personal information include your name, contact details, IP address, job applications and information about the pages you have viewed and the path you have taken through our Sites.
Your Consent
Please take a few minutes to review this Privacy Policy. By accessing or using this Site and accepting the use of cookies explicitly, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
You have the option once entering our site(s) to accept or decline the use of cookies and what cookies might be used for. We are also giving you the option to completely be anonymous, however this will impact the site functionality dramatically and only give you very limited information.
We also recommend to use the Google Opt-out plugin, found to be downloaded and installed here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
Changes to This Privacy Policy
As we add new features and functionality to our Sites, we may need to update or revise this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to do so, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version on our Sites. These changes will be effective as of the date we post the revised version on our Sites. They will apply only to the personal information we collect after we have posted the revised version. Your use of one of our Sites following any such change constitutes your consent to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. For this reason, it is important to review this Privacy Policy regularly.
If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will provide a notice at the top of this Privacy Policy for at least 30 days after the new effective date, so that you can see at a glance whether our Privacy Policy has changed since your last visit. You may access the current version of this Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the link marked “Axiell Group Online Privacy Policy” at the bottom of each page of our Sites.
Privacy Notices
This Privacy Policy may be supplemented or amended from time to time by “Privacy Notices” posted on our Sites. Generally, Privacy Notices provide details about the personal information we collect on particular pages or particular areas of a Site, why we need that information, and choices you may have about the ways we use that information.
What Personal Information Do We Collect Through Our Sites?
Information You Provide
We collect the personal information you knowingly provide (using your mouse and keyboard) when you use our Sites. The information we collect depends on how you use our Sites. For example, if you sign up to receive email communications from us, we collect your email address and any related information you provide. If you communicate with us using the “Contact Us” feature, we collect the information you provide when you complete the “Contact Us” form etc.
Generally, our sites distinguish between information we need in order to provide you with a particular product, service or to fulfill your request (“mandatory fields”), and information that although useful is optional with respect to that particular product, service or your request. Please be aware that if you do not provide us with mandatory fields we will not be able to provide you with the product or service or to fulfill your request.
Supplemental Information
From time to time, we may supplement the information you give us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address, information based on your zip code, or information about your business. We may also supplement the information you give us with information we collect from you through other Axiell Web sites and/or other channels. For example, if you are an Axiell customer, we may supplement the information you provide online with information you provide in your other business dealings with Axiell, or your social interactions with our company.
Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser
We collect information that is sent to us automatically by your Web browser. This information typically includes your IP address, the identity of your Internet Service Provider, the name and version of your operating system, the name and version of your browser, the date and time of your visit, your approximate location and the pages you visit.
An “IP address” is a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. It is used to identify your computer’s “location” in cyberspace and physically, so that the information you request can be delivered to you. If you use a dial-up connection or a connection that assigns dynamic IP addresses, your computer will be assigned a new IP Address each time you connect to the Internet. If, however, your computer is permanently connected to the Internet using a static IP address, the IP address assigned to your computer will generally be the same each time you use your computer. Although it does not identify you by name, we treat your IP address as your personal information.
You should be aware that when you respond to an electronic communication you receive from us, for example, by opening an email, downloading images or clicking on a link in an electronic newsletter, your browser tells us that you (or someone using your email address) has done so.
We use this information to improve our marketing efforts. In addition, we review our server logs – which contain visitors’ IP addresses – for security and fraud prevention purposes. If criminal activity is suspected, we may share our server logs and the personal information we have collected through this Site with the appropriate investigative authorities who could use that information to trace and identify individuals.
Cookies and Similar Technologies
A cookie is a small file sent by a Website and stored on a user’s computer which enables the Website to remember information about you and your preferences.  We use “cookies” and other Web technologies in a number of ways. For example, we may use these technologies:
to collect information about the ways visitors use our Sites – which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page;
to support the features and functionality of our Sites – for example, to save you the trouble of reentering information already in our database or to prompt the settings you established on previous visits to our Sites;
to personalize your experience when you use our Sites;
to measure the success of our web or email advertising.
We use cookies to adapt the content of our site, and advertisement to you of the site, apply functions for social media and analyze our traffic. We collect and send information about your usage of our site to those Social media, advertising and analysis companies we cooperate with, like Google, LeadFeeder, HootSuite, Facebook and Linkedin amongst others.
These companies can in their turn combine this information with other information you have shared, or they have collected, when their services have been in use.
The cookies we use can be classified into two categories:
“Session cookies” which are allocated to your computer for the duration of your visit of our Sites and which will be automatically removed from your computer when you close your browser.
“Persistent cookies” which expire after a reasonable period of time or until the user deletes the cookie.
Some of these uses may involve the use of “third party cookies”; that is, cookies that are set by software used by one of our service providers, such as to carry out statistical analysis of page use, page interactions and paths through the site, or for the purposes of serving internet advertisements using an online advertising supplier.
Generally, the information we collect using these Web technologies does not identify you by name. If, however, you have created a user identity, for example, signed up on a newsletter or by signing up to use a password-protected area on one of our Sites, we may link the information we collect using Web technologies to other information that identifies you personally.
If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete our cookies as soon as you leave a Site. For more information on how to do so, please refer to your browser ‘help’ section or see https://www.allaboutcookies.org or https://www.aboutcookies.org. You now have the option to accept or reject cookies through the cookie consent form, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you will not be able to use all of the features and functionality of our Sites.
How Does Axiell Use Your Personal Information?
Generally we use the personal information we collect through our Sites
to provide the products, information and services you request;
for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
to provide you with effective customer service;
to provide you with a personalized experience when you use our Sites;
to display personalized advertising when you visit our Sites;
to contact you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you;
to contact you with information and notices related to your use of our Sites;
to invite you to participate in surveys and provide feedback to us;
to better understand your needs and interests;
to improve the content, functionality and usability of our Sites;
to improve our products and services;
to improve our marketing and promotional efforts;
to enable remarketing features offered by Google;
to enable analysis through AdWords and targeted advertising through remarketing with google;
to enable Google Analytics;
to enable demographical insights through google tools; and
for any other purpose identified in an applicable Privacy Notice or other agreement between Axiell and you.
To Whom Do We Disclose Personal Information?
We may share the personal information we collect through our Sites for marketing and information purposes as described below:
Our Service Providers. We share personal information with companies and organizations, including subsidiaries and other business entities controlled by Axiell, that perform services on our behalf, for example, companies that provide Website support services to us. For some of these services (like the public social networks), we leverage their services for our social accounts connected to Axiell. The management of personal data is related to how the service themselves manage the data.
MailChimp
Facebook
LinkedIn
Twitter
Google
LeadFeeder
WordPress
YOAST SEO
Wistia
Microsoft
Sucuri
Within Axiell. We may share your personal information within Axiell Group (that is, among the business units within Axiell) and with any of our affiliates where there is a “need to know” for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Business Transactions. Axiell may decide, for strategic or other reasons, to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize one or more of its businesses. A transaction of this type may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective purchasers.
Business Transfers. Your personal information may be transferred to a company that has acquired the assets of Axiell or one of our business units, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization or liquidation.
Compliance With Laws and Protection of Our Rights and the Rights of Others. We may disclose personal information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose personal information to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce or apply our online terms of use or other agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.
As Described in a Privacy Notice. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as described in any Privacy Notice posted on the Web page where you provide that information. By providing your personal information on that Web page you will be consenting to the disclosure of your personal information as described in that Privacy Notice.
As Described in a Click-Through Agreement. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as described in any click-through agreement to which you have agreed.
Your Choices
We give you choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. If so, we may ask you to indicate your choices at the time we collect your personal information. If you have created an account or a personal profile on one of our Sites, you may be able to update some or all of your privacy choices by changing the settings on your account settings or profile page.
How Can You Access, Update or Correct or Delete Your Personal Information?
If you wish to access, update, delete or correct your personal information, please contact us.
We will respond to you within a reasonable time and within the time limits established by applicable law. We may ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In most cases, we will provide access if applicable and correct or delete any information you wish. In some cases, however, we may limit or deny your request if the law permits or requires us to do so or if we are unable to verify your identity.
Right to erasure (‘right to be forgotten’): You have right to request from us erasure of personal data or restriction of processing and to object to processing as well as the right to data portability. For information about how to get access to Personal Data and for exercising your rights, please refer to the contact points mentioned at the end of this Privacy Notice.
Security
Although we take commercially reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality, integrity and security of your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. For this reason we urge users to take every precaution to protect their personal information while using the Internet.
Links to Other Axiell Websites
Axiell operates many different Websites, each with its own content, features, and functionality. Each Axiell Website serves a different purpose. For this reason, not all of our Websites are governed by this Privacy Policy. When you use a link on one of our Sites to access another Axiell Website, take a minute to review the privacy policy posted on that Website.
Links to Third-Party Websites
This Site may also contain links to Websites operated by other companies, including websites operated by our third-party service providers, and unrelated third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information collected on any of these other Websites. When you access third-party Websites through a link on one of our Sites, please take a few minutes to review the privacy policy posted on that site.
Children’s Privacy
Our Sites are not directed at children under the age of 18, and we do not use our Sites to knowingly solicit personal information from or market to children under the age of 18. If we learn that someone under 18 has provided personally identifiable information through one of our Sites, we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our databases.
Special Notice for Visitors
Axiell is a global organization doing business in many countries and we may transfer your personal information across national borders for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Our headquarters are in Lund, Skåne Län in Sweden. Our Web servers and databases are stored by third parties such as Kinsta, Google and or inhouse servers in Lund, Sweden or in other countries and the information on these servers and databases may be accessed by our staff (or staff of our service providers) located in other countries where they have a “need to know”. Different countries have different privacy laws and requirements, and some, including the Swedish, provide less legal protection for your personal information than others. Please know, however, that no matter where your personal information is collected, used, transferred or stored, if it was collected through our Sites, it will be processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy and any privacy notices or click-through agreements that apply to you.
BY USING THIS SITE AND AGREEING TO ANY NUMBER OF COOKIES OF YOUR CHOICE, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE COLLECTION, USE, AND TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN OR TO SWEDEN OR ANY OTHER COUNTRY IN THE WORLD.
Questions About Our Privacy Practices
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, or want to get in contact:
Send an e-mail to: webmaster@axiell.com
Get the latest news in your mailbox with our newsletter
Select your areas of interest:
Newsletter list*
Libraries
Digital Media Distribution
Are you a customer?YesNoCountryPlease chooseAfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarrussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweYour email*
Accept integrity and GDPR policies* I have read and understood Axiell’s Privacy policyPhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Get the newsletter
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
We use cookies and collect other personal information on our website. To see how, why and what please read our Online Privacy Policy. By continuing using our site, you are accepting our Online Privacy Policy.
I understand
